LOGAN J. ZEHR

Cell: 260-438-7310 | Email: <u>zehrl315@outlook.com</u> | Seattle, WA 98112

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/logan-i-zehr | GitHub: github.com/zehrl | Portfolio: zehrl.github.io/developer-portfolio/

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer with 4 years of Manufacturing Engineering experience. Strengths in project management, cross-functional team collaboration & problem solving.

Projects

News Flow | Repo: github.com/CoryKDev/news-flow | Live: news-flow.herokuapp.com Interactive news experience that displays news articles based on location.

- Integrated backend for user authentication & article favoriting functionality (MongoDB, Express, JWT)
- Developed & integrated main page mockup & front end functionality (React, Bootstrap, Figma)

The Cocktail Generator | Repo: <u>github.com/zehrl/cocktail-generator</u> | Live: <u>zehrl.github.io/cocktail-generator</u> | Virtual bartender that provides cocktail recommendations based on time of day and weather conditions of user.

- Developed front end, REST API communication to pull & display cocktail information (jQuery, AJAX)
- Designed card components used for displaying results (Handlebars.js)

Eat the Burger | Repo: github.com/zehrl/burger | Live: <u>liz-eat-the-burger.herokuapp.com</u>

Personal project that allows users to create virtual burgers that can be "consumed."

Deployed application with emphasis on mobile first (MongoDB, Handlebars.js, jQuery, Bootstrap)

Experience

Manufacturing Engineer, Ingersoll Rand, Kent, WA

2020 - 2021

- Collaborated with site, cross-functional team daily to prioritize factory quality issues.
- Led project initiative to insource machined parts that increased earned hours for factory employees.

Product Manufacturing Engineer, Honeywell Aerospace, Redmond, WA

2019 - 2020

- Improved & developed current and future processes & documentation
- Managed two cost-savings projects resulting in ~\$25k savings per project

Rotational Engineer, Honeywell Aerospace, Redmond, WA

2017 - 2019

• Trained personnel & certified to factory processes per aerospace & site standards

Education

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

Purdue University, West Lafayette, IN